♪ Nobody knows ♪
♪ The trouble I've seen ♪
♪ Glory, hallelujah. ♪
(Penny:)Something got you down,
there, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Leonard kicked me out
of my own apartment.
(Sheldon:)And his app team.
(Penny:)Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)He wouldn't drive me
to work today.
(Sheldon:)I had to wear
my bus pants.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)And they're
still sticky.
(Sheldon:)Aw...
(Sheldon:)Probably going to have
to throw them away.
(Penny:)Hey, you don't need
Leonard and his app.
(Penny:)You can make one with me.
(Raj:)With you?
(Penny:)Seriously,
I have a great idea for one.
(Sheldon:)Is it better than your idea
to move to Los Angeles
(Sheldon:)and become a famous actress?
(Penny:)Okay, look...
(Penny:)when you see someone
wearing shoes you like,
(Penny:)you just snap a picture of them,
(Penny:)and the app goes on the Internet
(Penny:)to find out
where you can buy them.
(Sheldon:)That's your app idea?
(Penny:)Well, you don't like it?